

RAE MCGEE They/Them UX DESIGNER

EXPERIENCE

UX DESIGNER

Flex Rental Solutions (July 2022 - Present)

Creates user personas, recruits, scripts, and conducts early product phase user interviews and creates and user tests prototypes. Implements and maintains a UX Research Repository to track trends across multiple user studies.

Owns and collaborates on wireframes, mockups, and other UI supplements for the product team while maintaining a current components library in Figma.

SOFTWARE QUALITY ASSURANCE ANALYST

Flex Rental Solutions (July 2021 - July 2022)

QA Analyst: designed and executed manual test plans, developed automated tests for an inventory management web app, exploratory tested features for usability in an agile workflow, pre-release. Initiated and managed documentation for an import tool.

SOFTWARE QUALITY ASSURANCE ANALYST

Fusionbox (August 2018 - December 2019)

Created manual regression test plans for 15 clients' web and mobile applications, pioneered a test suite with Pycharm, Robot Framework and Selenium for a children's emotional intelligence platform. Documented client-reported bugs for development. Configured Django CMS for customers.

EDUCATION

Google UX Design Certification Candidate

University of Denver

Master of Music in Violin Performance

EXPERTISE

- User Research
- User Interviews
- Figma components

Launch Code

Full Stack Web

Development Bootcamp

Eastern Washington University

Bachelor Music in Violin Performance

- Wire frames
- UI mockups for user testing
- Classical music

ABOUT

UX Designer and Researcher - a creative and innovative empath who is genuinely curious about people. Infamous for asking great questions and is a caring, strong leader. Entered tech to become a developer after doing a full stack web development bootcamp, until someone saw their greatest strengths adding value to the early design phase. After being a UX consultant to many at their job, Rae now works in a full time UX Design role, where they lead the team through Design Thinking processes and generally have a lot of fun getting to know the user!

CONTACT

- ★ kerstimcgee@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/rae-mcgee
- (509) 294-1475
- Denver, CO